There are 4 which have created a stir in the market,
so in this video we will look at two features of each of those products
and see
whether the product really has power or is it just
for talk. The first product is
HDFC AGO Optimusic and the
first feature of product pickup is 2X wage, that is, in this
you get double coverage from De One, if it
is a policy of 10 lakhs then you get coverage of 20 lakhs
but you have to pay only a premium
of 10 lakhs. Its second feature
is reimbursement on paper basis, that is,
whenever any of your claims comes and goes into it through reverse print, then
you do
not need to give any physical document,
you can claim the company sitting at home
and you get your money. The second
product is New 2.2, its first feature is
Lock de Clock, that is, whenever you are
taking this product, the
premium you are paying at that time, if you do
not take a claim then its premium does not change, if the premium changes
from 425 to 55 seconds, its
tenth is No Claim Bonus, that is, if you do
not make any claim  If you take it, then every year the company
gives you 100% no claim bonus and it goes up to 10x, that is,
if your policy is of 10 lakhs, then
in 10 years your policy becomes of one crore. The
best feature is the next
company and the next product is
Tata Medi Premium of Tata Log. Its first feature is
your HI and diagnostic OPD coverage. Many
times it happens that there are
some symptoms of illness in our body due to which the
doctor makes us do HI and registry test,
which is not possible in normal health insurance,
but if it is Tata, then it
is possible. The second feature is the global coverage option. Many
times it happens that there are many treatments which are
not possible in India,
for which we have to go out of India. So
if you have a starting policy, then
global coverage option is given in it, so
you can go outside India and get your treatment done.
ICC Lombard Apex Plus
Thyroid BP or Sugar, its
waiting period is only two years and after that your
coverage starts. This is the second feature
and there is no average of ambulance,
you can use it till you are all insured.
If you want more information like this then
please subscribe, like and share that channel.